Mobile: 0404286785

Email: ajayghimire1998@gmail.com

Linkedln: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ajayghimire/

Website:

https://ajayghimire1998.github.io/ajayghimire

AJAY GHIMIRE

Full Stack Software Developer

"I have gone from slicing sashimis to slicing arrays"

PROFILE

Highly motivated and talented former Cook with 4+ years of work experience in high pressure and fast paced team environment, seeking an opportunity to establish a career in software development with passion, dedication, experience and extensive knowledge of web development, application development and integration with intuitive problem-solving skills under the belt. Proficient in JavaScript, Ruby, and their relevant frameworks. An empathic listener and persuasive speaker. Enthusiastic about self-learning, android development, and machine learning.

EDUCATION

ACADEMY XI
SYDNEY, NSW
Full Stack Software Engineering Transform
Feb 2022 – Aug 2022

VICTORIAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

SYDNEY, NSW
Bachelor of Information Technology
(Software Development)
2018 - 2021

TECHNICAL SKILLS

· Data structures and algorithms.

Programming Languages:

- JavaScript
- Ruby
- HTML and CSS
- Java (Actively Learning)

Frameworks:

- Front-end development with React JS, Next JS and Redux.
- Back-end development with Node JS, and Ruby-on-Rails.

Databases:

MYSQL, MONGODB, and PostgreSQL

EXPERIENCE

BRAND EASY AUSTRALIA, Campsie, NSW Intern Web Developer
Dec 2022 – Present

WOOLWORTHS CFC, Lidcombe, NSW Online Dispatch Member
Dec 2022 – Present

CHO CHO SAN, IZAKAYA, Potts Point, NSW Cook
Jan 2018 – Nov 2022

MCDONALDS, Cremorne, NSW *Customer Service*Dec 2017 – Feb 2019

PERSONAL PROJECTS

PROJECT	SOURCE CODE
WITH LOVE	https://github.com/AjayGhim
FROM HOME	ire1998/with-love-fromhome-
(React, Redux,	frontend (frontend)
Ruby-on-Rails,	https://github.com/AjayGhim
PostgreSQL,	ire1998/with-love-fromhome-
and AWS)	server (back-end)
PLAYMATES (Ruby-on-Rails and MySQL)	https://github.com/AjayGhim ire1998/Play-Mates
CRYPTOMANIA	https://github.com/AjayGhim
(Ruby)	ire1998/Crypto Mania RUB Y
MEMEBOOK (React and Firebase)	https://github.com/AjayGhimire1998/memebook
MOVIE FINDER	https://github.com/AjayGhim
(Native JS)	ire1998/Movie-Finder
GOALS-TO-	https://github.com/AjayGhim
SCORE (MERN)	ire1998/GoalsToScore